<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<docs>
  <summary>
    Writes character and color attribute data to a specified
    rectangular block of character cells in a console screen buffer.
    The data to be written is taken from a correspondingly sized rectangular
    block at a specified location in the source buffer.
  </summary>
  <param name="hConsoleOutput">
    A handle to the console screen buffer. The handle must have the <c>GENERIC_WRITE</c> access right.
    For more information, see
    <see href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/console/console-buffer-security-and-access-rights">Console Buffer Security and Access Rights</see>.
  </param>
  <param name="lpBuffer">
    The data to be written to the console screen buffer.
    This pointer is treated as the origin of a two-dimensional
    array of <see cref="ConsoleChar"/> structures whose size is specified by the <paramref name="dwBufferSize"/> parameter.
  </param>
  <param name="dwBufferSize">
    The size of the buffer pointed to by the <paramref name="lpBuffer"/> parameter, in character cells.
    The X member of the <see cref="Coord"/> structure is the number of columns;
    the Y member is the number of rows.
  </param>
  <param name="dwBufferCoord">
    The coordinates of the upper-left cell in the buffer pointed to by
    the <paramref name="lpBuffer"/> parameter. The X member of the <see cref="Coord"/> structure is
    the column, and the Y member is the row.
  </param>
  <param name="lpWriteRegion">
    A pointer to a <see cref="SmallRect"/> structure. On input, the structure members
    specify the upper-left and lower-right coordinates of
    the console screen buffer rectangle to write to. On output,
    the structure members specify the actual rectangle that was used.
  </param>
  <returns>
    <para>
      If the function succeeds, the return value is nonzero.
    </para>
    <para>
      If the function fails, the return value is zero.
      To get extended error information, call <see cref="GetLastError"/>.
    </para>
  </returns>
</docs>